Guide to the Washington State University Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center Photographs 1919-1969
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 1: Images created by WSU-Prosser staff, 1919-1969
  - Subseries 1: Dated images, 1919-1969
    - R. Moe's - Pasco Slope, Wash. Zn deficient corn plant, Idahybrid 544. Boawn. 4x5 neg.; print. 1949-09-30 (Box 5, Item 49.011)
    - Golden arborvitae grown from seed. Color. 2x3 neg. No print. 1949-05 (Box 5, Item 49.013)
    - Lima bean var. Clore. 5x7 neg. No print. 1949-09-29 (Box 5, Item 49.014)
    - Loc. A4. Varied damaged asparagus. (Clore?). 5x7 neg. No print. 1949-04-25 (Box 5, Item 49.015)
    - Loc: Roza D block. Apricot seedlings. Fogle. 2 5x7 negs. No prints. 1950-08-15 (Box 5, Item 50.001)
    - Cherry seedlings damaged by DMC spray 1:800. Fogle. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-01-08 (Box 5, Item 50.001)
    - Loc: Roza D block. Peach seedlings. Fogle. 2 5x7 negs. No prints. 1950-08-15 (Box 5, Item 50.002)
    - Loc: Bing orchard lower unit. Cherry Pollination Cage. Fogle. 5x7 neg. No print. WSUP208. 1950-07 (Box 5, Item 50.003)
    - Bartlett and Anjou Pears. Winter Injury. Fogle. 4x5 neg.; print. 1950-03 (Box 5, Item 50.004)
    - Stanley Prune. Fogle. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 5, Item 50.005)
    - Italian Prune. Fogle. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 5, Item 50.006)
    - Tragedy Plum. Fogle. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 5, Item 50.007)
    - Early Italian Prunes. Fogle. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 5, Item 50.008)
    - Duarte plum. Fogle. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 5, Item 50.009)
    - Weatherspoon Prune. Fogle. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 5, Item 50.010)
    - Yakima plum. Fogle. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 5, Item 50.011)
    - Pictures taken by Anna Jim. 1950 Field Day - Dr. Clore in bean and corn plots. 4 different 4x5 prints. No negatives. WSUP344, WSUP345. 1950-08-23 (Box 5, Item 50.012)
    - Walt's Grape Scene, Copywork. Clore. 4x5 neg.; print. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.013)
    - Taken by Anna Jim. 5 different prints of Dr. Stanberry and the Geiger Counter and Bill Julian in the booth at Field Day. 5 different 4x5 prints. No negatives. On the back of one print: "8/23/50 C.O. Stanberry and geiger counter 1950 Field Day. 1950-08-23 (Box 5, Item 50.014)
    - Taken by Anna Jim. Plant Pathology booth and plots. 5 different 4x5 prints, no negatives, no names. 1950-08-23 (Box 5, Item 50.015)
    - Taken by Anna Jim. Mr. Singleton, Dr. Buchanan, and a visitor in the hop booth on Field Day. 1 5x7 print, no negative. WSUP346. 1950-08-23 (Box 5, Item 50.016)
    - Taken by Anna Jim. Registration desk and Dave Cline and his chrysanthemums on field day. 2 different 4x5 prints, no negatives. 1950-08-23 (Box 5, Item 50.017)
    - Beet Plots, Hadley Farm, Toppenish, Washington. 4x5 neg.; print. 1950-11-08 (Box 5, Item 50.018)
    - Corn - fertility experiment Moses Lake Development Farm. Menzies. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP209. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.019)
    - Sugar beets on white background. 1 print, 2 identical 4x5 negatives. 1950-11-10 (Box 5, Item 50.021)
    - Sugar beets on white background. 4x5 neg.; print. 1950-11-10 (Box 5, Item 50.023)
    - Taken by Anna Jim. Carl Nelson holoding a discussion group on Field Day. 1 4x5 print, no negative. WSUP347. 1950-08-23 (Box 5, Item 50.025)
    - Taken by Anna Jim. Jim Menzies and two visitors in the potato field. 1 5x7 print, no negative. WSUP348. 1950-08-23 (Box 5, Item 50.026)
    - Taken by Anna Jim. Vic Bruns at his booth on Field Day. 1 4x5 print, no negative. WSUP349. 1950-08-23 (Box 5, Item 50.027)
    - Taken by Anna Jim. Kenneth Frick and his booth on Field Day. 1 5x7 print, no negative. WSUP350. 1950-08-23 (Box 5, Item 50.028)
    - Taken by Anna Jim. Jim Ballard and Dr. Merrill explaining Horticulture displays. 1 5x7 print, no negative. WSUP351. 1950-08-23 (Box 5, Item 50.029)
    - Ramsey vineyard. Zn SO4 dipped shoot showing recovery. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.030)
    - Ramsey Vineyard, Grandview. Zn chlorotic vines. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.031)
    - Black leaf of Concord cause unknown. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.032)
    - Zn and Fe chlorosis of Concord grapes correction. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.033)
    - Zn def and correction. Concord grape leaves. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-24 (Box 5, Item 50.034)
    - Zn and Fe chlorosis of Concord grapes correction. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.035)
    - Zn and Fe chlorosis symptoms. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.036)
    - Chas. Ramsey's Grandview. Zinc def. check and zinc dip. Clore. 5x7 neg. No print. 1950-08-30 (Box 5, Item 50.037)
    - Chas. Ramsey's. Zinc chlorosis Concord. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-30 (Box 5, Item 50.038)
    - Effect of P on cheat in alfalfa. Stanberry. 5x7 neg. No print. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.039)
    - Effect of P on cheat in alfalfa. Stanberry. 5x7 neg. No print. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.040)
    - E-4. Effect of P on cheat in alfalfa. Stanberry. 5x7 neg. No print. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.041)
    - Upper Unit E-29. Effect of non alafalfa establishment. Stanberry. 5x7 neg. No print. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.042)
    - Upper Unit E-29. Effect of non alafalfa establishment. Stanberry. 5x7 neg. No print. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.043)
    - Location: E20, 21, 22. Plot 8, 2nd block. Clore. 5x7 neg. No print. 1950-08-29 (Box 5, Item 50.045)
    - Church's Vineyard No. 5. Pruning 100 buds Umbrella High Trellis. Clore. 5x7 neg. No print. 1950-09-18 (Box 5, Item 50.046)
    - F-4 Lower unit. Red Mex Radioactive P plots. Clore. 5x7 neg. No print. WSUP210. 1950-08-27 (Box 5, Item 50.047)
    - Hormone plots C-39. 2,45-T injury on Fordhook 242. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-31 (Box 5, Item 50.048)
    - E-21 Roza. Lima beans. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-29 (Box 5, Item 50.049)
    - Roza E 51. Lima beans. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-06-29 (Box 5, Item 50.050)
    - E 21 Roza. Field bean fertilizer. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-29 (Box 5, Item 50.051)
    - Uniformity trials C-39. Beans at maturity. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP211. 1950-08-31 (Box 5, Item 50.052)
    - Insecticide plots. Aldrin 60 lbs. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-31 (Box 5, Item 50.053)
    - Insecticide plots. 3 lbs. Tech. BHC. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-31 (Box 5, Item 50.054)
    - E 20, 21, and 22 Roza. Insecticides in soil. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-29 (Box 5, Item 50.055)
    - Insecticide plots. Tech. BHC 15 lbs. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-31 (Box 5, Item 50.056)
    - Insecticide plots. 15 lbs. Lindone (Lindane?). Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-31 (Box 5, Item 50.057)
    - Insecticide plots. 238 lbs. DDT. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-31 (Box 5, Item 50.058)
    - Insecticide plots. Lindane 15 lbs. BHC Tech. 3 lbs. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-31 (Box 5, Item 50.059)
    - Insecticide plots. 238 lbs. DDT. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-08-31 (Box 5, Item 50.060)
    - Grape Mealy Bug on Concord from Wyant Orchard. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.061)
    - Ramsey Vineyard, Grandview. Zinc chlorosis. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.062)
    - E.J. Adams Vineyard. Fe chlorosis on Concord. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.063)
    - E.J. Adams Vineyard. Vine dead from symptoms of Fe chlorosis. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.064)
    - Ramsey Vineyard, Grandview. Zn chlorosis on Concord grapes. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-14 (Box 5, Item 50.065)
    - Nitrogen Percentage and Days After April 1. Jacobs. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.067)
    - Nitrogen Percentage and Tons of Dry Matter Per Acre. Jacobs. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.068)
    - Tons of Dry Matter Per Acre and Days After April 1. Jacobs. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.069)
    - Cherry seedlings in pots showing table outlay with peat moss. Ballard. 4x5 neg.; print. 1950-12-11 (Box 5, Item 50.070)
    - Seedlings in flats. Ballard. Wrong 5x7 negative in envelope. 1950-12-11 (Box 5, Item 50.071)
    - Cherry seedlings in pots showing albinos. Ballard. Wrong 4x5 negative in envelope; no print. 1950-12-11 (Box 5, Item 50.072)
    - Cherry Fruit fly and larvae. No negative in envelope. 1950-11-24 (Box 5, Item 50.073)
    - Cherry Fruit fly and larvae. 4 4x5 negs. No prints. 1950-11-24 (Box 5, Item 50.074)
    - Roza. Klingle's - Red Mexican Beans - Sagemoor Soil, right 3 rows sprayed with ZnSO4 on 7/7/50. Frank Viets. Klingle was a local farmer. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1950-08-01 (Box 5, Item 50.074a)
    - National Reclamation Experiment Station Exhibit - Spokane, Washington. 4x5 neg.; print. 1950-11-15 (Box 5, Item 50.077)
    - National Reclamation Experiment Station Exhibit - Spokane, Washington. 4x5 neg.; print. 1950-11-15 (Box 5, Item 50.078)
    - Steer Feeding negatives 1950-51. Heinemann. 51.63 also written on envelope. Two figures of weight gain and 3 4x5 negatives of some kind of crop, 1 with a person. 1950/1951 (Box 5, Item 50.079)
    - Insecticide plots aerial view - July 1950. 4x5 neg.; print. 1950-07 (Box 5, Item 50.080)
    - Genetic varigated Concord grape leaves. 4x5 neg.; print. 1950 (Box 5, Item 50.081)
    - Hormone like effect of 75 lbs. of Chlordane in the soil on Red Mexican and Black Valentine bean foliage. Clore. 7 5x7 negatives and prints. 1950-06 (Box 5, Item 50.082)
    - 2,4D symptoms on Concord grapes from Kennewick area. 8 35mm negs. 11 4X5 negs. 3 prints. Clore?. 1950-06 (Box 5, Item 50.083)
    - Vegetable Legume. Roza E 50-51. Clore. 4 5x7 negs; print. WSUP212. 1950-07-03 (Box 5, Item 50.084)
    - Charley Ramsey. Clore? Family photo of 5 people. 2.5x3.25 neg. No prints. WSUP213, WSUP214. 1950-08-14 (Box 5, Item 50.085)
    - Zinc deficiency symptoms on Concord Grapes. 5x7 neg. No print. 1950-07 (Box 5, Item 50.086)
    - Corral location in grapes showing Zn. Two other labels attached to envelope: Chas. Ramsey, Grandview Corral zinc deficiency. Chas. Ramsey's, Grandview, zinc chlorosis. Clore?. 1950-08-30 (Box 5, Item 50.087)
    - Church No. 5. Trellis - low vs high. Clore?. 5x7 neg. No print. WSUP215. 1950-09-18 (Box 5, Item 50.088)
    - Church #5, Kennewick. Pruning 100 buds Umbrella. Clore?. 5x7 neg. No print. 1950-08-18 (Box 5, Item 50.089)
    - Church No. 5. Pruning 100 buds, Kniffin. Some data written on back of print. Clore?. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 5, Item 50.090)
    - Church No. 6. Pruning 100 bud. Grower pruned. Clore. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 5, Item 50.091)
    - Church No. 5. Pruning - 100 buds Umbrella High Trellis. Clore?. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 5, Item 50.092)
    - Church No. 5. Pruning 100 bud spur. Clore?. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 5, Item 50.093)
    - Church No. 5. Trellis Low vs High. Clore?. 2 5x7 negs. Prints. WSUP216. 1950-09-18 (Box 5, Item 50.094)
    - Cherry seedlings in pre-treatment germination trials. Fogle. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-01-08 (Box 5, Item 51.003)
    - Cherry seedling showing genetic off-type leaves of cross 10. Fogle. 4x5 neg. No print. 1951-01 (Box 5, Item 51.004)
    - No Title. Wilton H. (Heinemann). Note inside envelope: Hold until Wilton sends caption over. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-01-06 (Box 5, Item 51.005)
    - No Title. Wilton H. (Heinemann). 4x5 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.006)
    - No Title. Wilton H. (Heinemann). 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP217. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.007)
    - No Title. Wilton H. (Heinemann). 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP218. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.008)
    - No Title. Wilton H. (Heinemann). 4x5 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.009)
    - No Title. Wilton H. (Heinemann). 4x5 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.010)
    - 2,4-D injured cane. Church No. 9. Clore. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-01-22 (Box 5, Item 51.011)
    - 2,4-D injured cane. Church No. 9. Clore. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-01-22 (Box 5, Item 51.012)
    - Church's #5, Kennewick. Umbrella Row 259 2# wood vine 12. Clore. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-01-22 (Box 5, Item 51.013)
    - Church's Kennewick. Randall weighing prunings. Clore. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP219. 1951-01-22 (Box 5, Item 51.014)
    - Church's #5, Kennewick. Umbrella pruned grapes. Clore. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-01-22 (Box 5, Item 51.015)
    - Butler Building. Ballard. West Building. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP220. 1951-01-28 (Box 5, Item 51.016)
    - Cherry seedling graft. 4x5 neg. No print. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.017)
    - Cherry friut fly bait trap. Frick. 3 4x5 negs. No prints. 1951-02 (Box 5, Item 51.019)
    - Cherry seedling terminal irregularity. Ballard. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP221. 1951-03-12 (Box 5, Item 51.020)
    - Cherry seedlings showing difference in vigor believed due to length of after-ripening time. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-03-15 (Box 5, Item 51.021)
    - Pollination cages over peach trees, Fogle. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. WSUP222. 1951-04 (Box 5, Item 51.023)
    - Cherry seedlings showing contrast in vigor prior to setting out. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-04 (Box 5, Item 51.024)
    - Cherry seedling showing root development outside pot. These were picked off four times at two week intervals prior to setting out in field. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-04 (Box 5, Item 51.025)
    - 1950 Ropac meeting. Initiation of new members including Nelson Shaulis. Wilton Heinemann, Harold Singleton, many others. 8 2.5x3.25 negs.; prints. WSUP223-WSUP225. 1950 (Box 5, Item 51.026)
    - Church - Benton City. Frost injury. Clore. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-05-16 (Box 5, Item 51.027)
    - Rotovater in grapes (Carl Morgan). Clore. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. WSUP226. 1951-06 (Box 5, Item 51.028)
    - Alfalfa damaged by Red-backed cutworm Euxoa ochrogaster, Grandview. Klostermeyer. Shows plants and larvae. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-05-21 (Box 5, Item 51.034)
    - Alfalfa damaged by cutworms. Note damaged tips. Grandview. Klostermeyer. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-05-21 (Box 5, Item 51.035)
    - Cotton maple scale on grapes. Clore. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1951-06-10 (Box 5, Item 51.038)
    - Toscle farm. Dieldrin on lima beans. Klostermeyer. House in background. 4x5 neg. No print. 1951-06-26 (Box 5, Item 51.039)
    - Roza E 20, 21 and 22. 8 II. 15# BHC/acre. Klostermeyer. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-06-26 (Box 5, Item 51.040)
    - Toscle Farm. Chlordane - lima. Klostermeyer. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-06-26 (Box 5, Item 51.041)
    - Roza - Menzies Spuds. Aphid trap. Klostermeyer. 4x5 neg. No print. 1951-06-27 (Box 5, Item 51.042)
    - Dead and dying cutworms (Euxoa ochrogaster) in bottom of irrigation rill in alfalfa dusted with 10% toxaphane - Grandview. Klostermeyer. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-05-21 (Box 5, Item 51.043)
    - O'Brien potato patch. Close-up of mite webbing. Klostermeyer. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-08-07 (Box 5, Item 51.045)
    - O'Brien potato field. Mite damage on potatoes. Klostermeyer. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-08-09 (Box 5, Item 51.046)
    - Close-up of gobs of mites on O'Brien potatoes. Klostermeyer. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-08-09 (Box 5, Item 51.047)
    - Close-up of gobs of mites on potatoes. Klostermeyer. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-08-09 (Box 5, Item 51.048)
    - McFail Trap. Frick. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP227. 1951-08-25 (Box 5, Item 51.049)
    - Mahaleb cherry showing importance only of 1st inch of cutting bed media. Graham. 2 5x7 negs. Prints. WSUP228. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.051)
    - Zn defcient Red Mexican bean plants, Roza B45. Boawn, Viets. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-09 (Box 5, Item 51.051a)
    - Robert F. Pyle - R#2, Box 175 - Kennewick. Front mount mower on Allis-Chalmers tractor. Clore. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. WSUP229. 1951-08-09 (Box 5, Item 51.052)
    - Church No. 6 - Kennewick. Alfalfa cones crop. Clore. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-08-09 (Box 5, Item 51.053)
    - Church No. 6 - Kennewick, Grape field with tractor. Clore. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-08-09 (Box 5, Item 51.054)
    - Roza. Zinc deficiency in alfalfa. Boawn. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-08-24 (Box 5, Item 51.055)
    - Response of alfalfa to two ZnSO4 sprays 30 days after application of the first. Roza C32. Boawn. Note inside envelope: negative loaned to Viets, Ft. Collins, 1/13/58, but there is a 4x5 negative. 1951-09-07 (Box 5, Item 51.055a)
    - Pictures for Frick's annual report. Mostly figures. 4x5 neg. No print. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.056)
    - Silage. Heinemann. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.057)
    - Silage. Heinemann. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.058)
    - Silage. Heinemann. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.059)
    - Cattle feeding. Heinemann. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.060)
    - A. H 61 Hogs. 15 prints, no negatives. Negatives in 51.005 to 51.010. 1951-01-06 (Box 5, Item 51.061)
    - Steer Feeding Bulletin grraphs, 1951. Heinemann. 4x5 neg. No print. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.062)
    - Church Vineyard Benton City. Mn defiency. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-09-24 (Box 5, Item 51.064)
    - A-36. Water deficit grapes. 4x5 neg. No print. 1951-09-24 (Box 5, Item 51.065)
    - A36. Young Concord grapes with Barley cover crop. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP230. 1951-09-21 (Box 5, Item 51.066)
    - Slighton - Kennewick. 32 bud cane bearing 21 shoots with 48 clusters. 2 4x5 negs. with people. No prints. WSUP231. 1951-09-17 (Box 5, Item 51.067)
    - Church No. 9. 2,4-D injured vine. 4x5 neg. No print. 1951-09-18 (Box 5, Item 51.068)
    - Roza E20, 21, 22. 24# DDT/Acre. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP232. 1951-09-24 (Box 5, Item 51.069)
    - Roza E20, 21, 22. Blk. Valentine foreground 119 purified. Backgrd 119 tech - DDT. 4x5 neg. No print. 1951-09-24 (Box 5, Item 51.070)
    - Roza E20, 21, 22. Insecticide in soil. #5 (238# DDT/A). 4x5 neg. No print. 1951-09-24 (Box 5, Item 51.071)
    - Roza E20, 21, 22. #8 (BHC 15#/A). 4x5 neg. No print. 1951-09-24 (Box 5, Item 51.072)
    - 24# DDT per acre. Ck above. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-09-24 (Box 5, Item 51.073)
    - Concord grapes - total wt. 28 oz. Clore. 4x5 neg.; print. 1951-09-51 (Box 5, Item 51.074)
    - Zn deficient grape vines (Concord variety). 3 5x7 negs. No prints. 1951-08 (Box 5, Item 51.075)
    - Foot Race for Seminar Secretary. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. WSUP233, WSUP234. 1951-09-28 (Box 5, Item 51.076)
    - Grape chlorosis and soil erosion in a Kennewick vineyard. Church #5. Clore. 4 2.5x3.5 negs. Prints. 1951 (Box 5, Item 51.077)
    - Purebred Herefords. Harold Singleton? Wilton Heinemann. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP235. 1952-02-25 (Box 6, Item 52.001)
    - Purebred Herefords. Harold Singleton? Wilton Heinemann. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-02-25 (Box 6, Item 52.002)
    - Purebred Herefords. Harold Singleton? Wilton Heinemann. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-02-25 (Box 6, Item 52.003)
    - Mint Still. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.004)
    - Mint Still. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.005)
    - Mint Still. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.006)
    - Hop Picking Mach. Dow. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.007)
    - Hop Picking Mach. Dow. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP236. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.008)
    - Hop Picking Mach. Dow. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.009)
    - Hop Picking Mach. Dow. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.010)
    - Cherry sampling device. Frick. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP237. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.012)
    - Mint Still. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.013)
    - Entrance Sign, IES. Field Day Publicity 8-52. 50s Plymouth with Oregon plates. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP238. 1952-08-08 (Box 6, Item 52.016)
    - Greenhouse. Oldemeyer, visitor, Law. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-08-08 (Box 6, Item 52.017)
    - Flag Raising. Frick, Heinemann and. Blurred. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP239. 1952-08-08 (Box 6, Item 52.018)
    - Greenhouse. Oldemeyer, visitor, Law. Field Day Publicity. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-08-08 (Box 6, Item 52.019)
    - Hop Field Day, 1952. Dow. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-08-08 (Box 6, Item 52.020)
    - Hop Field Day. Roza B-53. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP240. 1952-08-08 (Box 6, Item 52.022)
    - Beef Breeding Herd. Field B-5 west. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-08-08 (Box 6, Item 52.023)
    - Feeder's Day 1952. Charlie Kyd. 3-12-52?. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP241. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.024)
    - Beef Breeding Cattle. Field B-5 west. WWH. Wilton Heinemann in photo. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP242. 1952-08-08 (Box 6, Item 52.025)
    - Entrance Sign, Field Day Publicity 8-52. Similar to 52.016. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952-08-08 (Box 6, Item 52.026)
    - Feeder's Day, 3-12-52. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP243. 1952-03-12 (Box 6, Item 52.027)
    - Feeder's Day, 1952. 3-12-52?. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP244. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.029)
    - Feeder's Day 1952. WWH., M.E.E. 3-12-52?. 4x5 neg. No print. WSUP245. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.030)
    - Feeder's Day 3-12-52. Henry Anderson, W.W.H. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP246. 1952-03-12 (Box 6, Item 52.031)
    - Flag Raising, IES. Frick, Heinemann and Bry. Field Day publicity 8-52. Ken Frick, Wilton Heinemann and Bry. 4x5 neg.; print. WSUP247. 1952-08-08 (Box 6, Item 52.032)
    - 2,4-D Injury. Grape leaves. Labels inside envelope. 3 4x5 negs. Prints. 1952-07-19 (Box 6, Item 52.033)
    - 2-4-D injury, Positional study. Grape leaves. 3 4x5 negs. Prints. 1952-07-19 (Box 6, Item 52.034)
    - 128 (and?) 2,4-D on Concord grapes. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1952-03-06 (Box 6, Item 52.035)
    - Chas. Ramsey Vineyard, Grandview. Frost injury. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-05-17 (Box 6, Item 52.036)
    - Arvid Buchanan, 239 Div. St. Diseased Concords. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1952-05-17 (Box 6, Item 52.037)
    - Church No. 5. Vine 5, Row 184, 29 nodes, 44 buds. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. WSUP248. 1952-04-29 (Box 6, Item 52.038)
    - Church No. 5. Kniffin system well tied and spur system. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1952-04-29 (Box 6, Item 52.039)
    - Church 5. Umbrella system of pruning. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-04-29 (Box 6, Item 52.040)
    - Treatment from left to right, 512, 128, 32 fo 2,4-D on Concord. Lambda ? Symbol after treatments. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-04-11 (Box 6, Item 52.041)
    - Malformation from 32 (Lambda?) 2,4-D on Concord. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-04-11 (Box 6, Item 52.042)
    - treatment 16, 2,4-D on Concord. Lambda ? Symbol after treatments. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-04-11 (Box 6, Item 52.043)
    - Treatment 3-4-52. Treatment from left to right, 256, no treatment, 64, and 1 of 2,4-D on Concord. Lambda ? Symbol after treatments. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-04-11 (Box 6, Item 52.044)
    - Grape Clusters - Treated with 2,4-D. Whole Group - Black Background. 2 4x5 negs taped together. Prints. 1952-07-19 (Box 6, Item 52.045)
    - 2,4-D acid. Treatment of Concord grape leaves. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1952-07-19 (Box 6, Item 52.046)
    - No title but appears to be 2,4-D injury to grape leaves. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1952 (Box 6, Item 52.047)
    - Grape Clusters. 2,4-D injury. Whole Group - White Background. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-07-19 (Box 6, Item 52.048)
    - Cluster dif. Study in 2,4-D acid. 2 4x5 negs. Prints. 1952-07-19 (Box 6, Item 52.049)
    - Grape Cluster. compact group. White background. 2 4x5 negs. No prints. 1952-07-19 (Box 6, Item 52.050)
    - 2,4-D acid treatments made June 17, 1952. Picture taken 7-19-1952. 2 4x5 negs taped together. Prints. 1952-07-19 (Box 6, Item 52.051)
    - Treatment Juune 17. 2,4-D acid. Picture taken 7-23-52. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952-07-23 (Box 6, Item 52.052)
    - E-20, 21, 22. 238# DDDT. Left of picture 5 III. Right side 12 III. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952-05-22 (Box 6, Item 52.053)
    - Insecticide Plots. II-5 foreground, II-1 background. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952-05-02 (Box 6, Item 52.054)
    - Roza Insecticide Plots. Plot IV-8, 15# BHC. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952-05-02 (Box 6, Item 52.055)
    - 15# BHC/acre (8 IV). 24# DDT treat. Immediately above. 4x5 neg.; print. 1952-08-01 (Box 6, Item 52.056)
    - Insecticide Plots. 238 DDT. II-5 left, II-18 right. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952-05-02 (Box 6, Item 52.057)
    - Insecticide Plots. Plots I 4 back, 3 fore. 119 DDT. 4x5 neg. No print. 1952-05-02 (Box 6, Item 52.058)